To think we'd be trounced so thoroughly...
But that's Ike, I suppose.
Isaac's like a child--he just wants
to strut around with his new toy.
Has everyone evacuated?
It's underway. Have patience.
Yo, Elliot... Karen...
It's been a while, Ike.
You've sure made a violent entrance
for visiting an old friend.
I don't want much--
just to bring you
and Karen back to DEM.
If I refuse?
Well then, you'll just
have to play with me.
Beelzebub.
So be it. You've never been
one to listen to others.
Please, Elliot.
It's all right, Karen.
Now that I think of it,
this is the first time we've faced off.
Yeah. I'm shaking in my boots
at the very thought of it, Elliot.
Mukuro...
So that's Mukuro?
Michael.
Lataib.
Deploy Protect Territory!
Hmm?
Now you can reach her without a spacesuit.
Shido, it's do or die.
Got it. Send me to her.
It's the enemy. Four DEM ships.
Goetia... She got us good
before history was changed, but...
I'm glad to get a shot at revenge.
Deploy Dual Territory:
Spatial Control and Defense!
--Sir!
Time to teleport.
Mukuro's all yours, Shido.
Leave it to me! Stay safe, guys!
You're Shido, correct? I told you:
Muku doesn't want to be saved.
I didn't come to talk with you.
I'm here for the real Mukuro
whose heart isn't locked.
It was Muku who locked Muku's own heart.
Mind your own business.
But why would you lock your own heart?
What happened that--?
You're free to disregard my warning
just as Muku is free
to deal with you as I see fit.
I won't let my big brother get hurt!
Kotori!
Yup. We're using Territory to detect
and dodge incoming objects.
But don't over-rely on it.
You won't last getting hit by an Angel.
Got it! Thanks, Kotori! MARIA!
Haniel!
Hmm. I see...
An Angel you stole from a Spirit?
It's mean to say I stole it.
I'm borrowing it to save you!
Kaleidoscope!
What...?
Mukuro, I'm gonna open
your heart with this!
Commander, Bandersnatch.
That's not all! This response...!
Artemisia Ashcroft.
Kotori!
We'll fight, too.
I'll help, too!
We'll make the wind blow,
even here in the airless sky!
Agreement. We won't sit around
and do nothing.
So be it. I was hoping to keep
you guys out of the fight, but...
MARIA, it's time for that.
Origami can handle it.
Roger.
An emergency arming device...
AW-111, Brunhild. It's our latest model.
Put it to good use.
Territory hit! No damage!
Not even a greeting first?
Now that's a low blow.
Receiving transmission.
We meet again, Kotori Itsuka.
What do you want, Ellen Mathers?
For us to surrender?
That's right. I see you have a new ship,
but it's useless.
I'll just wreck it again.
I see. They must know, too:
that in the other world,
Fraxinus was destroyed by Goetia.
Beelzebub's power is impressive.
Your boss must be in good spirits.
Good spirits, you say?
That's not far from the truth.
I know. Otherwise, he wouldn't be
invading enemy bases himself.
Huh? What did you say?
Ike attacked Ratatoskr?
What, you didn't know?
Oh? I thought you were close,
but I guess he doesn't trust you.
If you think I'm lying, go check yourself.
Or are you scared to know?
Trying to rile me up won't work.
I'll simply check after the battle
is over. It won't take five minutes.
Enemy moving to surround.
Change of plans: only Tohka and Origami
go out. Everyone else, standby.
Aww! Why?!
Opinion. We can help, too.
I've got a plan.
For now, just do as I say.
Bring it on, my dear rival.
I'll show you the power
of the new Fraxinus.
Now then, shall we begin our date?
Lataib.
Zadkiel!
How strange. Are you truly human?
That's what I tell myself, at least!
Artemisia Ashcroft!
Sorry, but I'll be taking that Spirit!
--You okay, Shido?
--Origami!
Shido!
You okay, Shido?
Yeah! Thanks, Tohka!
Zadkiel!
Sandalphon!
--Fall back, Tohka!
--Are you sure?
I'm fine. Kotori, can you do me a favor?
Artemisia, why are you with DEM?
It doesn't make sense for you
to be friendly with them.
How do you know my name?
It doesn't matter. With you around,
it seems I can't finish my mission.
Sorry, but I'll have to destroy you!
You're strong. Way stronger than me...
as a Wizard.
That's...?
I see... You were there
when I came for Sister.
Good. If you're a Spirit,
I can kill you without guilt.
Deploy Yggdrafolium one through ten!
Converging magic power cannon,
Mistilteinn! Fire!
It's one of Fraxinus' new powers.
Modeled off Goetia, unfortunately.
Your power and maneuverability
have certainly increased.
However, those who challenge Heaven
will have their wings plucked.
Be scorched by the flames of God.
Who said we only had one trump card?
Thanks, guys. My Spirit power
alone wouldn't cut it.
Of course. I'm glad to help.
When we come together, we're unbeatable!
It's like all our Spirit powers
are mixing together!
Something about that
makes me really happy!
System Blōt:
a new weapon driven by Spirit power
which surpasses the limits of Territory.
This time, victory is ours!
Bite the dust, World's Strongest Wizard!
Only the small fry are left!
Let's clean 'em up!
You're still here?
You really don't learn, Shido.
I told you:
I came to unlock to your heart!
Michael!
--Let's go, Tohka!
--Mm!
Mm. I knew you'd try that.
Nice try, but it's over now.
Now, Shido!
You're kidding...
Who are you?
A neighborhood high schooler. Lataib!
Metatron!
Not bad--combining Spirit power
and generative magic.
Goetia!
You've lost. Give it up.
I'm afraid you're wrong.
Our goal... is to take out the Spirits!
Shido!
Mukuro!
Zadkiel!
--Shido!
It's all right, Mukuro!
I'll protect you!
Nice to meet you. I'm going to be
your new mother. And this is Dad.
Nice to meet you.
I'll be your sister, so let's get along.
--Shido!
--Boy!
--Darling!
What's wrong, Shido? You're crying?
Uh, it's just from a dream I had.
Where is this?
Fraxinus' infirmary. It wasn't easy
catching you out of the sky.
Oh, yeah... And Mukuro?!
What about Mukuro?!
We don't know. During the fall,
you got separated.
For real?! Then--!
Muku is right here.
--Mukuro?!
What a mean guy, making Muku wait.
But it's fine. I'm in a good mood now.
Eh? Uh, huh?
Such a sourpuss.
Is this because your heart opened up?
Convinced. And her emotions have returned.
E-Even if that's true...
Mukuro, you're so different now.
Is it odd for Muku's heart to be touched
by the one who worked hard to open it?
The moment it was unlocked,
I felt grateful for
everything you've done.
Though, the reason I'm fond of you is...
Let's see...
Just because?
Hey, hey...
Yes, just because. I feel like
you and Muku are close.
Close?
Anyway, since it seems
you haven't recovered yet,
I shall return tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow, Mister.
Didn't see that coming! That was Mukuchin?
Her personality's nothing like I heard!
Surprise. I had imagined
a very rude Spirit.
But what a cutie. Her body is tiny,
but she's big where it counts.
Darling is such a perv!
She said she'll come tomorrow.
What then, Shido?
Uh, well...
Enough, enough! We'll discuss that later.
Shido's still healing up.
The ship has some new facilities.
Why don't you go soothe your body?
"New facilities"?
"Bath"
"Fraxinus"
A bath imbued with magic, huh?
It's true--I do feel great!
But what was that dream all about?
That little girl was...
Washing yourself while injured
won't be easy. I'll help, Shido.
Whoa, whoa! I'll be fine!
Leave it to me.
I'll lick--wash you clean.
You just said, "lick"!
Darling! I came to wash your back!
Shido, feeling better?! I'm here to help!
Liking the healing bath?!
Reminisce. When it comes to bathing
together, you want the Yamai Sisters.
Guys! Shido came here to heal,
so let's not forget that!
Clearly, all of us didn't need to come.
But bathing with everyone will be fun!
I know! How about you and Yoshino
wash each other's backs?
Y-You wouldn't mind?
Whew! All these cuties
make for such a nice view!
Ike!
We may have shook hands a bit too hard.
I guess Elliot was incredibly
glad to see me.
Then, it's true?
You attacked Ratatoskr's base?
Yeah. But unfortunately,
I let Elliot slip away.
And your little sister, too.
Still, with Realizers,
I'll be on my feet tomorrow.
You didn't fare so well, either.
Due to my shortcomings. I deserve
whatever punishment comes my way.
But, Ike, you owe me an explanation.
Why didn't you tell me about Elliot?
If I had brought you, wouldn't you have
killed Elliot without question?
Ready, Shido?
Yeah, but where am I meeting Mukuro?
Am I going back to space?
That's the big question. She said
she'd come back, so we think she will...
It's time, Mister.
Shido!
Huh?
We're here on the surface,
just like you wanted!
You said there're lots of
fun things to do here!
So, let's get going, Mister!
"Episode 06:
'An Opened Heart.'"
Shido has opened Mukuro's heart.
As a new battle begins,
a new Origami and Tohka awake.
Next time: "Locked Memories."
"Episode 07: 'Locked Memories.'"
Be tasty! Moé Moé Kyun!